(Leonard:)Where did you go to school?
(Colonel Williams:)MIT.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
Well, hey, me, too.
(Colonel Williams:)I should have known.
(Colonel Williams:)Behind every great invention
is an MIT mind.
(Colonel Williams:)I'll cut to the chase.
(Howard:)The Air Force
believes there's an application
(Colonel Williams:)for this technology,
(Colonel Williams:)and we're interested
in funding your research.
(Howard:)Well, thanks,
but you should know
(Howard:)we're a little concerned about
this being used in weapons.
(Howard:)Oh, well,
let me put your mind at ease.
(Colonel Williams:)What we use it for
is none of your business.
(Leonard:)I don't know how
I feel about this.
(Colonel Williams:)Look, guys,
it's just a guidance system.
(Colonel Williams:)It's not like
you're handing us
the Death Star from Star Trek.
(Colonel Williams:)All you need to
worry about is,
(Colonel Williams:)right now, it's this big,
(Colonel Williams:)and we need it to be...
this big.